本∶告诉我这不是戈尔巴乔夫.这是资源.铁,我可以拿其中的一个.
Ben: Tell me that's not Gorbachev.OK, it's resources.
碳酸钾,妈妈,我们家的碳酸钾在哪里呀?
Iron; I can get one of those.Pottash.Mom, where do we keep the Pottash?
开萝尔∶妈妈正在洗澡.这些都是什么呀?
Carol: She's in the bathroom.What is all this?
本∶你不会知道的!
Ben: You can't tell!
开萝尔∶用脚趾画出的俄国地图.
Carol: A map of Russia, drawn by keeping a pen between your toes.
本∶俄国还有另一种东西,丑女人.
Ben: That's another thing Russia has; ugly women.
开萝尔∶你本应该在去年九月接到任务时就开始准备的.
Carol: You should have been working on this since you got the assignment
last September.
本∶为什么?明天才交呢.嗨!不要碰俄式色拉汁.
Ben: Why?it's not due till tomorrow.Hey, don't touch the Russian dressing.
开萝尔∶为什么?
Carol: Why?
本∶因为我用它来做自然资源.
Ben: Because I'm using it as a natural resource.
有压力我的工作才会做的更好.
I do my best work under pressure.
开萝尔∶本,你浪费了太多的时间了.
Carol: Ben, you spend far too much time procrastinating.
本∶你怎么知道的?
Ben: You know about that?
开萝尔∶大家都知道.
Carol: Everybody knows about it.
本:如果你晚交一次也许就不会有这么大压力了.
Ben: Well maybe if you procrastinated once in a while you wouldn't be
so tense!
杰森∶啊!本,这些是什么
Jason: Aarrgh!Ben, what's all this?
本∶康尼翰女士留的作业---我的地图工程.
Ben: My map project for Mrs.Cunningham.
杰森∶这是你九月份的时候就开始做的那个吗?
Jason: Is this the one you were griping about back in September?
本∶不是,是另一个.
Ben: Err...no, it's another one.
麦琪∶红色方形是什么?
Maggie: What's that red square?
本∶红色方形!你们是怎么想的?
Ben: Red Square!What's with you people?
杰森∶本,如果你需要帮助,只管说.
Jason: Well, Ben if you need any help, just ask.
本∶你可以带我去买一些浆糊吗?
Ben: Can you take me to get some paste?
杰森∶不行,不行,
Jason: No, no, no, no.Your mother and I have a...
不行.你妈妈和我订了一个位子,我们不能迟到的.
reservation and we can't be late.
本∶那么,在你走之前,
Ben: Yeah well, before you go,
你最少能告诉我,我们的碳酸钾在哪里吧?
can you at least tell me where we keep our Pottash?
迈克∶不必担心,有我在呢,我马上就吃好了.
Mike: Hi guys!Don't worry, I'm not staying, I'm just eating.
杰森∶嗨!对!迈克可以带着你去买浆糊.
Jason: Hey, there it is!Mike can take you to get the paste.
迈克∶本居然上了我的新车!
Mike: Ben in my new car!
麦琪∶迈克,他应该不会把你座位染色或怎么样的..
Maggie: Mike, it's not like he's going to stain the seats or something
迈克∶哦!但是妈妈,
Mike: Oh, but Mom, I've got plans, I've got big plans!
我已经有计划了,大计划!我才没有时间照顾这个小淘气呢.
I don't have time to take care of this little bozo.
杰森∶迈克!这个小淘气正巧是你的弟弟哦.
Jason: Mike!Come on this little bozo happens to be your brother.
现在就带他去商店,马上.
Now take him to the store...now.
迈克∶好吧,我进去拿个三明治,然后再来和小家伙纠缠.
Mike: Great, I come in to get a sandwich and I wind up with a weeny.
迈克∶你真的需要浆糊吗?
Mike: Do you really need this paste?
本∶是的迈克,我必须完成一个三度地图的作业.
Ben: Yeah Mike, I have to do a 3 D map for school.
迈克∶老康尼翰女士?嗨嗨,她还活着?
Mike: For old Mrs.Cunningham?Hey hey, is she still alive?
本:是啊,还在给我布置作业.你还要做一个土耳其地图么?
Ben: Enough to give me homework.Did you have to do a Turkey map too?
迈克∶本,才不是呢.
Mike: No Benny, it was my finest academic hour; I got Monaco.
那是我最好的学习时间;我做的是摩纳哥地图.我只简单的把一张扑克牌条粘贴到3/5的卡片上,
I glued one poker chip to a three by five card and I was home free!
就搞定了!可怜的泊纳尔是的是俄国;做错了800万平方米的路.
Poor Boner got Russia; eight million sqaure miles of ways to go wrong.
那你呢?你做哪个国家的地图?
So, what country did you get?
本∶开你的车,行不?
Ben: Just drive, OK?
迈克∶嘿,爸爸给了我足够多的钱来买浆糊,不是吗?
Mike: Hey look, Dad gave me enough money for this paste, right?
本∶还有零钱.
Ben: Exact change.
迈克:好,我在这里等你.
Mike: Alright, I'll wait here; the less I'm seen with you the better.
本∶对,无论如何.
Ben: Right, whatever.
迈克∶你干什么?
Mike: What are you doing?
本∶我忘记了拿梳子.
Ben: I forgot my comb.
迈克∶本,你是要买浆糊,现在你要梳子干什么?
Mike: Benny, you're buying paste, now what do you need your comb for?
本∶嗨,你不会明白的.
Ben: Hey, you never know.
迈克∶本,你不可能在那里遇见像她们这样的可人儿.哈罗!
Mike: Benny, it's not like in there you're gonna run into a couple of babes
like them.Well, hello
女孩1∶嗨.
Girl 1: Hi.
迈克∶2位小姐今天晚上过的好吗?
Mike: Well...err...how are you two ladies this evening?
女孩2∶还好.
Girl 2: OK.
迈克∶你们低估了自己.
Mike: You underestimate yourselves.
女孩1∶你们在干什么?
Girl 1: So, what's up?
本∶哦我们正在买一点浆糊.
Ben: Oh, we're just buying a little paste.
女孩∶粘粘的,粘粘的,粘粘的.
Girl 1: Sticky, sticky, sticky.
本∶你不是说不需要我的梳子吗?
Ben: And you said I wouldn't need my comb.
迈克∶本!你要去哪里 ?
Mike: Benny, where are you going?
本∶去买浆糊.
Ben: I'm going to get my paste.
迈克∶本,别想浆糊了!快来,我们走!
Mike: Benny, forget the paste!Come on, let's go!
本:去哪儿?
Ben: Where?
迈克∶跟着她们!
Mike: After 'em, now!
本∶不,不,不!本,快上车!
Ben: No, no, no!Benny, in the car!
迈克∶在那里!她们在那辆红色的大众车里!
Mike: There!There they are in the red Votswagen!
本∶迈克,你确信我们要这样做吗?
Ben: Mike, are you sure we should be doing this?
迈克∶本!这是我们生存的意义所在!
Mike: Oh come on Benny!That's what we were put on this earth to do!
我们是男人.
We're guys.
本∶但是我们要去哪里呢?
Ben: Yeah, but where are we going?
迈克∶跟着我们的小姐们.只要有美女,
Mike: Wherever our women are going.
去哪里都可以.
That's the beauty of it; it could be anywhere.
本∶你认为我们要去的地方会不会也有浆糊?
Ben: Do you think there'll be some place there'll be paste?
迈克∶是的.我敢肯定我们要去的地方一定会有很多很多的浆糊!我敢打赌那里会有一屋子的浆糊.
Mike: Oh yeah, oh I'm sure there'll be lots and lots of paste where we're
going!I bet there'll be a whole house of paste
本∶好,我明白了.迈克,
Ben: OK, I get it.Come on Mike, they're getting away!What are you doing?
他们已经走了!你在干什么?我以为我们在追她们!
I thought we were chasing them!
迈克∶天,她们闯红灯了!
Mike: Man, they ran the light!
本:你是侦探么?快啊,迈克,怎么了?
Ben: So what are you, a boy scout?Come on Mike, work it what's happening?
警官∶你们刚才在后面的路上开的有点快了,不是吗?
Police Officer: You boys were going a little fast back there, were'nt you?
本∶不够快;女孩们都跑掉了!
Ben: Not fast enough; the girls got away!
警官∶我明白了!
Police Officer: I see!
迈克∶别理他,军官,他是我们家的耻辱.
Mike: Ignore him officer, he's the shame of the family.
本∶他是对的,我不知道自己在做什么.
Ben: He's right, I don't know what I'm doing.
我才不想追女孩呢,我只是想完成我的立体地图的作业.
I didn't want to chase girls, I wanted to finish my 3 D map for school.
警官∶康尼翰女士的家庭作业?嗨,她仍活着?
Police Officer: For Mrs.Cunningham?Hey, is she still alive?
本∶是呀.你当初做的是哪个国家?
Ben: Yeah.So what country did you get?
警官∶俄国.
Police Officer: Russia.
本∶我也是.你做的怎么样?
Ben: Same here.What'd you do?
警官∶我还在画呢.嗨!
Police Officer: I'm still working on it.Hey look...err...
你们的问题已经够多了,忘记罚单吧.
you boys got problems enough, forget the ticket.
迈克∶哈哈,谢谢长官!
Mike: Ha ha, yes sir!
警官∶我找碳酸钾找了20年了.
Police Officer: I've been looking for Pottash for twenty years.
迈克∶哦,真棒,我刚才逃过了一张罚单!
Mike: Oh yes, I just beat a ticket!
本∶是我帮你的.
Ben: And I helped.
杰森∶对!
Mike: Yeah!
本∶就像我跟开萝尔说过的,有压力我会把事情做的更好.
Ben: Like I was telling Carol before, I do my best work under pressure.
迈克∶让我们去找你的浆糊.
Mike: Let's go get your paste.
本∶嗨!迈克,靠边!!
Ben: Hey Mike, pull over!!
迈克∶什么?什么?哪儿?你看见女孩们了吗?
Mike: What?What?Where?Did you see the girls?
本∶我听到了!唷哈啧,发生什么啦?
Ben: I heard that!Yo Haz, Bagee, Raphee, what's up?
臭虫∶本,你在真正的车里干什么?
Stinky: Ben, what are you doing in an actual car?
本∶哦,我和本刚才正在追女孩子呢,躲避警察;你知道,经常的.
Ben: Oh, me and Mike have just been chasing babes, ducking cops; you know, the usual.
虫∶哇.
Stinky: Wow.
男孩:我哥哥不让我搭他的车;他怕我弄脏他的座位.
Boy: My brother won't even let me go in his car;
he's afraid I'll stain the seats.
臭虫∶嗨!迈克,漂亮的轮子!
Stinky: Hey Mike, nice wheels!
迈克∶嗨!谢谢你臭男人,从一个驾驶员嘴里说出来更有分量.
Mike: Hey thank you stink man, that means a lot coming from a jockey.
男孩∶里面呢,怎么样?
Boy: So, how's the interior?
迈克∶是乳白色的,并且不会退色.
Mike: It's ice-cream free, and it's gonna stay that way.
本,我们走吧,去买你的浆糊.
Come on Benny, we need to get your paste.
臭虫∶浆糊!你还没有完成你的地图?喔喔.
Stinky: Paste!You haven't done your map yet?Wooo.
本:谁在乎你的可恶的地图? 我们在兜风!我们走,迈克.
Ben: Hey, who cares about a stinking map?We're cruising here!Let's roll, Mike!
迈克∶唷呼!埃迪!
Mike: Yo ho, Eddy!
埃迪∶迈克尔,你坐在改装小飞车里面干什么?
Eddy: Michael, what are you doing in Soho flying a car?
本∶啊,本和我正在躲避女孩子,
Mike: Ah, Benny and I are just ducking babes and chasing cops!
追警察呢!你知道,经常的.
You know, the usual.
本∶哈?
Ben: Huh?
埃迪:好.
Eddy: Yeah right!And picking up a few Bucks for babysitting the bozo, huh?
迈克∶没错.
Mike: Yeah.
本∶呵呵,如果不是从驾驶员口出说出来的,我都不会介意!
Ben: Yeah, I wouldn't mind that if it wasn't coming from a jockey.
迈克∶嘿本,本,你看!!
Mike: Hey Benny, Benny look!!
女孩∶粘粘的,粘粘的,粘粘的.
Girls: Sticky, sticky, sticky!!
本∶女人!
Ben: Women!
埃迪∶你们的女人!
Eddy: Your women!
迈克∶是的,那些女人正在追我和本,哈!
Mike: Yeah, those women are after me and Ben, ha!
本∶你没听见吗?她们在追迈克和我.
Ben: Didn't you hear the man?They're after Mike and me.
埃迪:如果你们有人不能寄,
Eddy: Yeah, well if one of you is unable to fulfil the duties of you post,
我在这里等.
I'm in there.
本∶走!
Ben: Go!
埃迪∶喔喔!
Eddy: Woooo!!
本∶嗨!迈克,迈克!!
Ben: Hey Mike, Mike!
迈克∶怎么了?怎么了?
Mike: What?What?
本∶明天还要上学呢,迈克!
Ben: It's a school night, Mike!
埃迪∶借过,迈克尔.
Eddy: Excuse me Michael, man.
迈克:求你.
Mike: Please.
本∶你又打到我了,我要把我的座位往后移移!
Ben: You hit me again, I'm gonna move my seat back!
迈克∶本,你自己选吧,俄国还是女孩.
Mike: Ben, here's your choices; Russia or Sticky sticky sticky.
本∶我们走.
Ben: Let's roll.
迈克∶埃迪,你有多少现金?
Mike: OK Eddy, how much cash you got?
埃迪∶哦!通常的.
Eddy: Oh, the usual.
迈克∶我也是.本,拿出你的胶水钱.
Mike: Man, me too.Ben pull out your glue money.
本∶我只有1块8毛9分.
Ben: I only got a Buck, eighty nine.
迈克∶等等.大家马上检查一下座位!
Mike: Err...one moment.Everybody, check the seats, now!
埃迪∶迈克尔,这是什么?
Eddy: Michael, what's this?
迈克∶是...
Mike: That's......
埃迪∶哦,我的天!!
Eddy: Alright, my man!!
本∶哦!哇!
Ben: Oh wow!
迈克∶你兴奋什么?
Mike: What are you so excited about?
本∶我也不知道.
Ben: I don't know.
埃迪:13美分!
Eddy: Thirteen Cents!
迈克∶13美分!
Mike: Thirteen Cents!
埃迪∶好了,我们进来了!我们进来了!
Eddy: Alright, we're in!We're in!
本∶是的!
Ben: Yes!
埃迪∶迈克尔!!减速,我们要先为本找个小女孩.
Eddy: Alright, Michael!!Wait slow down, we've got to find a girl with a training
bra for Ben
迈克∶她们在那里,在那里!
Mike: There they are, there they!
本∶我们走!
Ben: Let's go!
杰森∶亲爱的,你为什么要擦挡风玻璃?
Jason: Honey, why are you cleaning the wind shield?
麦琪∶哦!因为我看不见电影.
Maggie: Oh, because I can't see the movie.
杰森∶我带你来不是看电影的,是为了和你...
Jason: I didn't bring you here for the entertainment,
你明白我说什么的.
I brought you so that we could make-out.You know what I mean.
麦琪∶宝贝儿,如果有人看见我们怎么办?
Maggie: Honey, what if someone sees us?
杰森∶谁会看见我们?
Jason: Come on, who's gonna see us?
哪个庸俗的人会来汽车电影院呢?
What kind of sleazy people come to a drive-in?
麦琪∶你.
Maggie: You.
杰森∶说对了.
Jason: Exactly.
迈克∶抱歉,请问到汽车电影院怎么走?
Mike: Excuse us, could you tell us which way to the drive-in?
女孩∶啊,就在你后面.
Girl 1: Ah, it's right behind you.
迈克∶哦!
Mike: Oh.
女孩2∶你为何不过来正对着正方呢?我是迪尼斯,
Girl 2: Why don't you come over here and face the right way?
她是沙拉.
I'm Denise, and this is Shana.
迈克∶你好,我是迈克.
Mike: Ah, hi, I'm Mike.
女孩1∶那个小家伙是谁?
Girl 1: Who's the little guy?
本∶我叫本.
Ben: I'm Ben.
女孩2∶不是问你,傻子!他.
Girl 2: Not you, silly!Him.
埃迪:小家伙!你知道他们所谓的小家伙,是么?
Eddy: Mmmm, little!Well, you know what they say about little guys, don't you?
女孩1∶事实上,我从来没有听到任何人谈论过矮男人.
Girl 1: Actually, I've never heard anybody say anything about little guys.
埃迪∶谁要被辱骂?走了,伙计,我们走!
Eddy: Well, who needs this abuse?Come on guys, let's go!
迈克和本∶再见!
Mike and Ben: See ya!
女孩1∶本,找到你的浆糊了吗?
Girl 1: Found any paste yet, Ben?
本∶还没有呢.找浆糊读对我来说就像一场梦一样.
Ben: Na.looking for paste seems like a dream to me now.
埃迪∶我已经有5英尺6英寸半了,并且还在长呢.
Eddy: I am five foot six and a half, OK?And still growing.
杰森∶我们为什么要买烤玉米片?
Jason: Why do we have to get Nachos?
麦琪∶我很饿,你没请我吃晚餐.
Maggie: I'm starving, you lied to me about dinner.
埃迪∶也许我应该给她们看看我背上的毛,这样她们才会明白.
Eddy: Maybe I should show 'em the hair on my back, that'll get 'em.
杰森∶你好,埃迪.
Jason: Hi, Eddy.
埃迪∶你好西维尔先生!
Eddy: Hi Mr.Seaver!
杰森∶我因为工作关系来这里的.
Jason: I'm here professionally.
杰森∶恩,我也是.
Eddy: Yeah, me too.
杰森∶和我的妻子.
Jason: Here with my wife.
本∶爸爸在这里干什么 ?
Ben: What is Dad doing here?
迈克∶我也不知道.按理说,他应该要去吃晚餐的.
Mike: I don't know.He was supposed to be going to dinner.
本∶也许他走桃花运了.
Ben: Maybe he got lucky.
迈克∶本,结婚的男人是不会走桃花运的..
Mike: Ben, married guys never got lucky
女孩2∶打扰一下.
Girl 2: Excuse us.
埃迪∶小姐!聪明的女士不理木头一样的兄弟.
Eddy: Ladies!Smart move dusting the deadwood twinski.
本∶不是她们不理我们,是我们不理她们.
Ben: They didn't dust us; we're dusting them.
女孩∶什么?
Girls: What?
迈克:我们不想打扰谁,我们马上走.走吧,埃迪.
Mike: Look, we're not dusting anyone, we just gotta leave.Let's go, Eddy.
埃迪∶嘿,唷,迈克,我为什么要离开?
Eddy: Hey, yo, Mikey, why do I gotta split?
本∶因为她们不喜欢你.
Ben: Because they don't like you.
女孩∶出了什么事 ?
Girl 1: What happened?
女孩2∶什么怎么回事?
Girl 2: What happened to what?
女孩1∶你太饿了.
Girl 1: You were too hungry.
女孩2∶不是.他们正在离开!启动车!启动车!
Girl 2: Was not.They're getting away!Start the car!Start the car!
本:迈克,
Ben: So Mike, what do you say we go back to the store and get two
你看我们会商店再找两个女孩怎么样?
more girls?
埃迪:那小家伙认为容易.
Eddy: Listen to the lad, he thinks it's so easy.
他不知道让一个女孩不讨厌你有多难,是把,
He doesn't know the hours of hard work it takes,
迈克.
just to get a girl to look you in the eye and not puke, right Mike?
迈克∶我不知道你在说什么,埃迪.
Mike: I don't know what you're talking about Eddy.
埃迪∶我并不是说呕吐,我是说讨厌的走开.
Eddy: Well, I didn't mean puke I meant, turn away with a sick look.
迈克∶嘿!
Mike: Hey!
本∶什么?
Ben: What?
迈克∶我们被跟踪了.
Mike: I think we're being followed.
埃迪∶哦!谁会跟踪我们?
Eddy: Oh, who'd follow us?
本∶也许妈妈和爸爸认出了我们!
Ben: Maybe Mom and Dad spotted us!
埃迪∶哦!对,我在汽车电影院看见你爸爸了.
Eddy: Oh yeah, I caught your dad at the drive-in.
迈克∶你刚才为什么不告诉我们.
Mike: And you're just now telling us!
埃迪∶我不觉得它很重要.
Eddy: Well I didn't feel it was germaine
本∶甩掉,迈克,甩掉他们!!
Ben: Lose Mike, lose 'em!!
迈克∶没问题!
Mike: Alright, alright, no problem!
埃迪∶哦!哦!我觉得我们真的被跟踪了!
Eddy: Oh oh, I think we're being followed!
本∶我可以吗?
Ben: May I?
迈克:可以.伙计!快.就好了.
Mike: Of course.Guys!Guys!Guys!Cut it out!Come on!We've got to go get 'em.
本∶你在驾驶!
Ben: You're driving!
迈克∶哦!是的.
Mike: Oh yeah.
埃迪∶西维尔,你在哪里买到这个好家伙的?
Eddy: Oh, Seaver, where did you purchase such a fine machine?
迈克∶好了,当我说现在的时候,
Mike: OK, when I say now, you pop the clutch,
你就放开离合器,引擎一启动你就把它拉回来!
once the engine starts you pop it back in!What are you doing?
你在做什么?我有说过刹车吗?
Did I once mention the word, brakes?
本∶我饿了!
Ben: I'm hungry!
迈克∶你饿了!你为什么要挑在这个时候饿呢?
Mike: You're hungry!You pick a time like now to be hungry?
本∶不是我挑的,是我的胃!
Ben: I didn't pick it, my stomach did!
埃迪∶嘿迈克尔,我也饿了.
Eddy: Hey I could eat too, Michael.
迈克∶伙计们,女孩们怎么办?
Mike: But guys, what about the girls?
埃迪∶她们讨厌我,记得吗?
Eddy: Well they hated me, remember?
迈克:我是说,钱呢?我们没有钱.
Mike: And I mean, what about the money?I mean, we have no money!
本∶让我来.
Ben: Allow me.
迈克∶是谁?
Mike: Who's that?
本∶是福朗西斯,是我们的一个同学.
Ben: That's Francis, a kid from my class.
埃迪∶我才不吃大排档,除非它们的味道真的不错.
Eddy: Now I'm not eating garbage out of some alley, unless it's really good.
本∶放松!你们想要汉堡包吗?
Ben: Relax!You guys want burgers?
迈克和埃迪:是的.
Mike and Eddie: Yeah.
本∶好吧,3份汉堡包.还要油炸食物吗?
Ben: Alright, three burgers.Anybody for fries?
迈克∶当然.
Mike: Sure.
埃迪∶是的.给我点洋葱圈,我今天晚上会很孤独的..
Eddy: Sure.Oh, make mine onions rings, I'm gonna be alone tonight
迈克∶都是洋葱圈!
Mike: All of that for onion rings!
本∶恩,只希望福朗西斯明天的地图课会走好运.
Ben: Ah no, I was just wishing Francis good luck on his map tomorrow.
迈克∶哦!哦!太伟大了!
Mike: Oh!Oh man, this is great!
埃迪∶是的,他给我们带来食物,带来女孩,我们应该更多的带他出来玩.
Eddy: Yeah.He gets food, he gets girls, we should bring him out with us more often.
迈克∶没错.
Mike: Yeah.
埃迪∶细想一下,谁需要你?
Eddy: Come to think of it, who needs you?
迈克和我还从来没有这么接近过...
Mike and I have never really been all that close...
本∶好了,我准备好了.
Ben: Alright, I'm ready.
埃迪∶嘿,我的朋友说他准备好了,出发!
Eddy: Hey my friend says he's ready, come on!
迈克∶现在记得,当我说现在,你就松开这离合器..
Mike: Now remember, when I say now, you pop the clutch...
本∶你之前说过了,我明白.
Ben: You said before, I got it.
迈克∶接着,就是刹车,本,刹车!
Mike: That was then, this is now.The brake Benny, the break!
埃迪∶他现在根本就不需要我们了.
Eddy: He doesn't want either one of us now.
本∶哦,我还没死,我还没丝.太好玩了,我都不会开车.
Ben: Oh I'm alive...I'm alive, I'm alive!This is fun.Err...I'm not driving.
警官∶你觉得这是在干什么?
Police Officer: Well what do you call it?
本∶车子自己开动,我只是控制方向而已.应该感谢我.
Ben: Well, it was just going and I was just stearing.I should be thanked.
警官∶你差不多有13岁了,对吗?
Police Officer: You're about thirteen, right?
警察无线电∶军官需要援助!军官需要援助,
Police Radio: Officer needs assistance!
16干线上.
Officer needs assistance, sixteenth on main.
警官∶孩子,今晚你很幸运.
Police Officer: Kid, this is your lucky night.
迈克∶本!本!本!出了什么事 ?你跟警官说什么了?
Mike: Benny!Benny!Benny, what happened?What did you tell the cop?
本∶我不知道?我只是希望他能离开,结果他真的走了.
Ben: I don't know?All I did was wish he'd go away and he did.
迈克∶好了,在爸妈还没从电影院回来时,我们要快点回家.
Mike: OK, let's get you home before Mom and Dad's movie lets out.
本∶对,上.
Ben: Alright, hop in.
迈克∶好.
Mike: OK.
本∶对.
Ben: Right.
埃迪∶好了,已经够近了.我的车在后面.
Eddy: OK, this is close enough.My car's just down at the end.
迈克∶好吧.埃迪!
Mike: OK.Eddy!
埃迪∶怎么了?
Eddy: What?
迈克∶是杜威特!
Mike: It's Dawitt!
埃迪∶我们的校长?
Eddy: Our Principal?
迈克∶没错.
Mike: Yeah.
本∶伙计们,你们已经毕业2年了.
Ben: Guys, you graduated two years ago.
迈克∶哦!嘿嘿,杜威特先生.漂亮的短裤!
Mike: Oh!Hey hey, Mr.Dawitt.Nice shorts!
杜威特先生∶好,好,好,
Mr.Dawitt: Well, well, well, Seaver, Zaff,
西维尔,查福,见到你们2个真是太好了.
how wonderful it is not to see you two any more.
埃迪∶谢谢杜威特先生,你也是.
Eddy: Thanks Mr.D, you too.
本∶杜威特先生,我们见过面了.
Ben: Mr.Dawitt, we've met.
杜威特先生∶我知道你个小鬼头.
Mr.Dawitt: I know that you little Gnat.
埃迪∶嘿,杜威特先生,不错的鸟笼
Eddy: Hey, Mr.D, attractive poultry.
杜威特先生∶你们在外面聚会?
Mr.Dawitt: Well, you boys out casing the joint?
迈克∶噢不,杜威特先生,我们只是四处兜兜风.
Mike: Oh no, Mr.D, we're just kind of cruising around.
杜威特先生∶好好享受,有冷风吹袭,
Mr.Dawitt: Well enjoy these times boys, there's a cold wind blowing;
人每年都会成长,
each year you get a little older and slip further and further away from
会离这些心灵的释放越来越远.在你察觉前,
these care-free jaunts.
蓦然回首,
Before you know it, one day you look back and a night like this is maybe,
你会发现这样的夜晚,才是你人生当中最美的.
just maybe, the best night of your life.
迪迪∶威利斯,不是你的雪茄在冒烟吧?
Didi: Willis, that isn't your cigar smoke is it?
杜威特先生∶迪迪,亲爱的.你们见过我太太吗?
Mr.Dawitt: Did darling.Have you boys met the Mrs?
男孩们∶没有!
Boys: No!
杜威特先生∶好的.
Mr.Dawitt: Good.
迪迪∶威利斯,不要这么性情乖戾的.大家好,我是迪迪杜威特.
Didi: Willis, don't be so grumpy.Hi, I'm Didi Dawitt.
迈克∶我是迈克西维尔.
Mike: I'm Mike Seaver.
迪迪:我听说过你.不过我想象中的你更高,
Didi: Say, I've heard of you.
更凶.
But somehow I pictured you taller, angrier and armed.
迈克∶;谢谢你.
Mike: Well, thank you.
埃迪∶我是爱德华查福.
Eddy: And I'm Edward Zeff.
迪迪∶我没有听说过你呢.
Didi: Well I've never heard of you.
本∶我此时记不得我的名字了.
Ben: I can't remember my name right now.
迪迪∶我敢肯定你的名字肯定很吸引恩.走吧,巴别塔,我们回家.
Didi: Charming, I'm sure.Come on babeling, let's go home now.
杜威特先生∶在你身后呢,宝贝儿.
Mr.Dawitt: Right behind you, honey.
迈克∶杜威特先生今天看来比以前要感觉好很多.
Mike: Well, it looks like there's a little more to Mr.Dawitt, than meets the eye.
本∶他真幸运,还能有2只眼睛.
Ben: He's lucky he hasn't lost an eye.
埃迪∶嘿,以后再找你们.
Eddy: Hey, I'll catch you guys later.
迈克∶好的.嘿,埃德,你现在开什么车?
Mike: OK.Hey, say, Ed, what are you driving these days?
埃迪∶很普通的,就在下面.
Eddy: Oh, err...nothing special, it's just down there.
迈克∶哦,哪儿?
Mike: Oh, yeah, where?
埃迪∶就在下面的转角处.
Eddy: Yeah, just down at the corner.
迈克∶哦,哪个车?
Mike: Oh yeah, which car?
埃迪∶自行车.自行车,好不好?别再笑我了!
Eddy: The bike.The bike, OK?Get off my back!
本∶我们走.
Ben: Let's go.
迈克∶等等,本,你没有忘记什么东西吗?
Mike: Wait a minute, Benny, haven't you forgotten something?
本∶我的浆糊!太好了!杜威特先生说的对,这是我生命中最好的一个夜晚.
Ben: My paste!Great!Mr.Dawitt was right; this was the best night of my life.
迈克∶嘿本,
Mike: Hey Benny, you didn't do so bad for a guy who started out with exact
你今天做的不错.
change for paste.
本∶你可以想像吗,在城市的某个地方,
Ben: Can you imagine, somewhere in the city,
正有一个女孩子在梦见我.
there's a girl dreaming about me, right now.
女孩∶你们这些家伙太险恶了.
Girl 1: You guys are nasty boys.
本∶嘿,我们本来要来找你们,但是,他想去吃宵夜.
Ben: Hey, we were gonna come looking for you but err...he wanted to eat.
女孩2∶你们这个周末还会兜风吗?
Girl 2: You guys gonna be cruising this weekend?
本∶恩.
Ben: Ah...see...errm...
迈克∶嗨,你明知道我们会的.
Mike: Hey, you know we will.
女孩2∶周末见.
Girl 2: See you then.
女孩1∶有点小礼物要送给我的粘性男孩.
Girl 1: Here's a little present for my sticky boy.
本∶浆糊.
Ben: Paste.
迈克∶本,不要被粘到了.
Mike: Ben, don't get any one ya.
迈克∶本,我很累.
Mike: Benny, I am beat.
本∶什么,你不帮我做地图工程了?
Ben: What, you're not gonna help me with my map project?
迈克∶本,你现在还要做你的地图?几乎是午夜了.
Mike: Benny, you're gonna do your map now?It's almost midnight.
本∶还有8个小时就要交了.
Ben: It's due in eight hours.
迈克∶本!你不累吗?
Mike: Benny, aren't you tired?
本∶迈克,我从来没像现在这么想睡觉.
Ben: Mike, I don't think I'll ever sleep again.
麦琪∶迈克,在这个时侯你还和本在外面干什么?
Maggie: Mike, what are you and Ben doing out at this hour?
迈克∶我们...
Mike: We were err...
杰森∶告诉我,你们不是刚刚买完浆糊回来.
Jason: Tell me, you're not just getting home from buying paste.
本和迈克∶我们不是刚刚买完浆糊回来.
Ben and Mike: We're not just getting home from buying paste.
杰森∶稍等,你们...
Jason: Look, just a second, you...
迈克∶你们的晚餐怎么样?
Mike: How was your dinner?
麦琪∶还不错.
Maggie: Ah...fine.
本∶这样说来是在餐厅,而不是在汽车电影院啦?
Ben: So, it was a sit down place, not a drive-in?
杰森∶汽车电影院?哦,
Jason: A drive-in?
驾车,我们必须要开车进去,我们必须要在车里.
Oh, driving, we had to drive in, in the car, we had to.
麦琪∶我们不需要在午夜站在车道上讨论饭店吧?
Maggie: Err, but do we really wanna stand in the drive-way in the middle
你认为他们知道吗?
of the night and talk restaurants?I think not.Do you think they know?
杰森∶当然不,麦琪.他们只是孩子!
Jason: No, of course not Maggie.They're just kids!
本∶嘿看看,他们忘记了我们.
Ben: Hey look see, they forgot about us.
迈克∶没错.
Mike: Yeah.
本∶嘿,你起来吃第2个汉堡了?
Ben: Hey, you up for another burger?
迈克∶本,你的地图完成的怎么样了?
本∶压力越大,我做的越好.
00:22:10,400
Mike: Benny, what about your map? Ben: I do my best work under pressure.